ELIK ARAD

E: <u>Arad.Elik@Gmail.com</u> M: +66 (0) 830141080

Suan plu soi 8, Sathorn Rd. Bangkok, Thailand 10120

PROFILE

Experienced implementation manager for a leading market online travel management platform.

Specialist in online travel\tourism and telecom technologies, with a strong IT background (14 years) in both Scrum and Waterfall development environments.

Committed to excellent on-time performances, quick and effective at decision making and crisis management.

Out-of-the-box thinking and strong interpersonal skills.

EXPERIENCE

2015 - Present Agoda.com Operations Manager

Bangkok, Thailand

- Conducted walk through, requirements gathering meetings and worked with the stakeholders to ensure the right solution.
- Evaluated information gathered from different sources\connectivity partners, reconciled conflicts, decomposed high requirements level requirements.
- Performed Unit testing to confirm accuracy, quality and completion as determined by the established requirements.
- Reported defects along with QA team and follow up with the Development lead to resolve outstanding defects.
- Managed the requirements, development, implementation and maintenance of systems, tools and workflows.
- Worked closely with connectivity partners to develop and support xml connections to Agoda XML API.
- Managed operational project tasks to improve efficiency between inter departments.
- Composed technical documents and user certification documents.

2012 - 2015 Insource Asia Co.,Ltd Bangkok, Thailand Implementation and Account manager

- Lead and managed the implementation process of new customers.
- Account management for existing clients.
- Provided input to Project Managers and Resource Managers for the

- prioritization of new and existing projects\developments.
- Gathered and analyzed business requirements from different sources including the client and third party vendors. Facilitated and participated in meetings with the client to clarify business requirements as mapped to functional and technical specifications and identified gaps.
- Converted requirements into user stories.
- Participated in sprint planning meetings.
- Acted as a subject matter expert when business requirements changed, and determined how the changes impacted the existing business processes and workflows.
- Provided input and reviewed project scope documents and work orders for accuracy.
- Facilitated and participated in project wrap up and lessons learned meetings.
- Performed Unit testing to confirm accuracy, quality and completion as determined by the established requirements.
- Reported defects along with QA team and follow up with the Development lead to resolve outstanding defects
- Provided reports on the project schedule to senior management as well as supporting other team members to ensure project success.
- Accountable for delivering the system on time to clients based on a defined road map (B2B, B2C, Backoffice, Suppliers Extranet, XML connectivities)
- Covered Local and Regional Market: Singapore, Malaysia,
 Thailand, India, Hong Kong, China, Dubai and Egypt.

2000 - 2010 Comverse Networks Systems Tel Aviv, Israel Senior Software developer

- Design and development of ISMSC (Intelligent Short Message Service Center) system.
- Release management responsibilities.
- Developed customer oriented features
- Integrated 3rd party software modules.
- Scripting of customers utilities
- Ongoing problems resolutions
- Composed technical and user documentations
- On-site installations and support.
- Maintained software integration\compatibility between different releases

EDUCATION

1996-1999 The College of management Tel Aviv, Israel

Behavioral Sciences and Management (Bachelor's degree)

1999-2000 John Bryce academy Tel Aviv, Israel

• Internet programming for academicians